Contact

surbhi.soni@iplaceusa.com LinkedIn Profile

Top Skills · See all

Human Resources · Marketing · Microsoft Office · Leadership · Team Management · Teamwork · Management

Accomplishments · See all

2 Languages

Surbhi Soni

Associate Recruiter at iPlaceUSA

Pune, Maharashtra, India

Summary

I am a highly engaged Associate Recruiter who is committed to helping talented individuals achieve their career goals. My expertise placing qualified talent in the Information Technology, Manufacturing, Marketing and Sales, Finance, Healthcare and Pharmaceutical space has led to winwin situations for both my candidates and clients. When not contemplating the mysteries of...

Read more

Experience

Associate Recruiter · iPlace

May 2019 - Present · Pune Area, India

• Thorough knowledge of recruiting process from sourcing to recruiting for different employment types including W2, Corp-to-Corp, 1099 for U.S. Citizens, GC, H1-B, TN-1, and EAD holders.• Hands-on experience with Applicant Tracking Systems (ATS) including Bullhorn and CATS.• Active Search: Resume search of activ

Recruitment Coordinator · Technicolor

June 2018 - December 2018 (7 months) · India

Intern · Courtyard by Marriott

April 2016 - May 2016 (2 months)

Education

M.S. Ramaiah Instt. Of Mgt

Post Graduate Diploma in Management (PGDM), Marketing and HR · (2015 - 2017)